Guide to the David Plowden Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1948-2011; Series I; 189; 41.9 linear_feet
  - July 1995 Acquisition
    - Reproducible Prints and Study Prints
      - Schoharie Creek Aqueduct, Built 1841. Erie Canal, New York (NYS-1067) Reproducible print, 1967 October (Box 90)
      - Schoharie Creek Viaduct, Built 1841. Erie Canal, Fort Hunter, New York (NYS-1067-8-4) Reproducible print, 1967 October (Box 90)
      - The Sciotoville Bridge, Ohio River, Chesapeake Ohio Railroad. Sciotoville, Ohio (GFB-68-84) Reproducible (plus) print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - Sioux City Bridge, Missouri River, George S. Morison, Engineer. Sioux City, Iowa (GFB-68-410) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - Sioux City Bridge, Missouri River. Sioux City, Iowa (969-408) Reproducible print, 1969 September (Box 90)
      - Sioux City Bridge, Whipple-Murphy Truss, Missouri River, George S. Morison, Engineer. Sioux City, Iowa (GFB-68-537) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - The Starrucca Viaduct, Erie Lackawanna Railroad. Lanesboro, Pennsylvania (273-24) Reproducible print, 1973 February (Box 90)
      - St. John's Bridge, Willamette River. Portland, Oregon (GFB-68-106) Study print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - Susquehanna River Bridges. Harrisburg, Pennsylvania (GFB-469-225) Reproducible print, 1969 April (Box 90)
      - Swing Bridge, St. Louis Bay. Duluth, Minnesota (GFB-68-2498) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - Town Lattice Truss Covered Railroad Bridge, St. Johnsbury Lamoille County Railroad, Missisquoi River. Swanton, Vermont (STJ-571-321) Reproducible print, 1971 May (Box 90)
      - Town Truss, Double Web, St. Johnsbury Lamoille County Railroad. Scranton, Vermont (STJ-571-176) Reproducible print, 1971 May (Box 90)
      - Town Truss, Double Web, St. Johnsbury Lamoille County Railroad. Scranton, Vermont (STJ-170-571) Reproducible print, 1970 January (Box 90)
      - Transporter Bridge. Duluth, Minnesota (GFB-68-6039) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - The Tunkhannock Viaduct. Nicholson, Pennsylvania (273-143) Reproducible print, 1973 February (Box 90)
      - The Tunkhannock Viaduct. Nicholson, Pennsylvania (273-78) Reproducible print, 1973 February (Box 90)
      - The Tyrone Bridge, Kentucky River. Tyrone, Kentucky (GFB-68-830) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - Walnut Street Bridge, Susquehanna River. Harrisburg, Pennsylvania (GFB-469-9) Reproducible print, 1969 April (Box 90)
      - Washington Bridge, Harlem River, Built 1888, Seen from Beneath Alexander Hamilton Bridge, Built 1962. New York, New York (HDP-24-3) Study print, 1966 (Box 90)
      - Washington Street Bridge, [Susquehanna River], Douglas Parabolic Patent Truss. Binghamton, New York (GFB-69-821) Reproducible print, 1969 (Box 90)
      - The West End, North Side Bridge, Ohio River. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (PB-567-1506) Reproducible print, 1967 May (Box 90)
      - The Wheeling Bridge, Ohio River. Wheeling, West Virginia (GFB-68-971-4) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - Whipple Bowstring Truss Bridge, Normanskill Farm. Albany, New York (GFB-69-858) Study print, 1969 (Box 90)
      - The Williamsburg Bridge, East River. New York, New York (173-44) Reproducible print, 1973 January (Box 90)
      - The Wire Bridge, Carrabassett River. North New Portland, Maine (GFB-69-1311) Reproducible (plus) print, 1969 (Box 90)
      - Yaquina Bay Bridge. Newport, Oregon (GFB-68-4812) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - Yaquina Bay Bridge, Conde B. McCullough, Engineer. Newport, Oregon (GFB-68-2814) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - Yaquina Bay Bridge, Oregon Coast Highway, Route 101, Conde Balcom McCullough, Engineer. Newport, Oregon (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 90)
      - [Ellis Island Ferry]. New York City Harbor (NYH-FB-E1-562) Reproducible (plus) print, 1962 May (Box 91)
      - Abandoned Grain Silo By Abandoned Rock Island Railroad Right-of-Way. Geronimo, Oklahoma (969-94) Reproducible print, 1969 September (Box 91)
      - Along Chicago Northwestern Railroad Tracks. Chicago, Illinois (181-38) Reproducible print, 1981 January (Box 91)
      - Ames Memorial Hall (Town Hall), H.H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-1031) Reproducible print, 1965 September (Box 91)
      - Ames Memorial Hall (Town Hall), H.H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-1009) Reproducible print, 1965 September (Box 91)
      - Ames Memorial Hall (Town Hall), H.H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-1017) Reproducible print, 1965 September (Box 91)
      - Anaconda, Montana (CP-1412) Reproducible (plus) print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - Atlanta, Georgia (HDP-3713) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 91)
      - Bank of Arizona. Bisbee, Arizona (678-1066) Reproducible (plus) print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Barn Door. Near Steam Corners, Ohio (975-1808) Reproducible print, 1975 (Box 91)
      - Beowawe, Nevada (CP-1307) Reproducible (plus) print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - Bloomingdale's. Manhasset, New York (174-383) Reproducible print, 1974 January (Box 91)
      - Building Adjacent to Erie Railroad Tracks, Opposite Depot. Montgomery, New York (No number extant) Study print, undated (Box 91)
      - Cape May, New Jersey (1072-6) Reproducible (plus) print, 1972 October (Box 91)
      - Carriage House, Ames Home (H.H. Richardson, Architect). North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-158) Reproducible print, 1965 September (Box 91)
      - Carter, Montana (GP-315) Reproducible (plus) print, 1971 (Box 91)
      - Catskill, New York (1073-459) Reproducible print, 1973 October (Box 91)
      - Chicago, Illinois (881-778) Reproducible (plus) print, 1981 August (Box 91)
      - Chicago, Illinois (1078-77) Reproducible print, 1978 October (Box 91)
      - Chuck Wagon. Near Sweetwater, Wyoming (GP-222) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 91)
      - Church Doorway. Falls Mills, West Virginia (374-743) Reproducible print, 1974 March (Box 91)
      - Churchyard. York, Pennsylvania (LFC-955) Reproducible print, 1964 April (Box 91)
      - Clear Cut. Upper Peninsula, Michigan (680-471) Reproducible print, 1980 June (Box 91)
      - Cleveland Cliffs Mining Corporation, Taconite Plant, Empire Mine. Palmer, Michigan (679-228) Reproducible print, 1979 June (Box 91)
      - Cleveland-Cliffs Coporation's Taconite Plant, Empire Mine. Palmer, Michigan (679-591) Reproducible print, 1979 June (Box 91)
      - Coal Mine. Sesser, Illinois (ISC-196) Reproducible print, 1980 (Box 91)
      - Company Store (Closed). Bisbee, Arizona (678-1058) Reproducible (plus) print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Culvert, St. Johnsbury Lamoille County Railroad. Near Morrisville, Vermont (STJ-571-540) Reproducible print, 1971 May (Box 91)
      - Dan Ryan Expressway. Chicago, Illinois (HDP-3342) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 91)
      - Danville, Kentucky (374-330) Reproducible print, 1974 March (Box 91)
      - East Calais, Vermont (V-NH-865-105) Reproducible print, 1965 August (Box 91)
      - East Chicago, Indiana (473-148) Reproducible print, 1973 April (Box 91)
      - East of Las Vegas, New Mexico (471-174) Reproducible print, 1971 April (Box 91)
      - Electric-Power Shovel, Dolomite Quarry. Gulliver, Michigan (ISM-42) Reproducible print, 1979 (Box 91)
      - Empire Mine. Palmer, Michigan (979-148) Reproducible print, 1979 June (Box 91)
      - End of I-20. Atlanta, Georgia (HDP-3603) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 91)
      - Farm. West Virginia (374-1153) Reproducible (plus) print, 1974 March (Box 91)
      - Faulk County, South Dakota (CP540) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 91)
      - Ferry Boat Beacon, Newburgh Ferry at Newburgh Slips, Hudson River. Beacon, New York (NBF-161) Study print, 1961 (Box 91)
      - Ferry Boat Dutchess, Newburgh Ferry (Before Being Burned and Rebuilt). Approaching Beacon, New York.(NBF-161) Study print, 1961 (Box 91)
      - Ferry Boat Orange, Newburgh and Beacon Ferry. Beacon, New York (No number extant) Study print, undated (Box 91)
      - Ferry Boat Orange Approaching Newburgh, Newburgh-Beacon Ferry. Hudson River, New York (NBF-1163-182) Study print, 1963 November (Box 91)
      - Ferry Collector, Liberty Street Terminal. New York, New York (CNJ-467-492) Reproducible print, 1967 April (Box 91)
      - Ferryboat Lackawanna, Hoboken Ferry, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad. Hoboken, New Jersey (EL-1167-314) Reproducible (plus) print, 1967 (Box 91)
      - Ferryboat Scranton Laid Up at Hoboken Ferry Terminal, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad. Hoboken, New Jersey (EL-1167-851) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 91)
      - Forest City, Pennsylvania (573-91) Reproducible print, 1973 May (Box 91)
      - Former Old Colony Railroad (New Haven Railroad) Depot, H.H. Richardson, Architect. Near Easton, Massachusetts (865-252) Reproducible print, 1965 August (Box 91)
      - Former Textile Mill. Lawrence, Massachusetts (1174-227) Reproducible print, 1974 November (Box 91)
      - Former Textile Mill. Lawrence, Massachusetts (1174-225) Reproducible print, 1974 November (Box 91)
      - Georgetown, Colorado (678-706) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Gila Bend, Arizona (678-1020) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Grain Elevator. Rush City, Kansas (CP-382) Reproducible (plus) print, 1982 March (Box 91)
      - Grain Elevator. North Topeka, Kansas (GFB-68-4850) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 91)
      - Grain Elevator and Windmill. Enid, Oklahoma (GFB-68) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 91)
      - Grain Elevator. North Topeka, Kansas (GFB-68-4581) Reproducible (plus) print, 1968 (Box 91)
      - Grain Elevators. Enid, Oklahoma (GFB-68-4628) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 91)
      - Grain Elevators. Russell, Kansas (969-80) Reproducible (plus) print, 1969 September (Box 91)
      - Grain Elevators. Superior, Wisconsin (GFB-68-2500) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 91)
      - Grain Elevators by Great Northern Railway Tracks. Carter, Montana (GP-1654) Reproducible (plus) print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - Grain Elevators by Great Northern Railway Tracks. Carter, Montana (GP-1655) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 91)
      - Graveyard. Danville, Vermont (ST-571-250) Reproducible print, 1971 May (Box 91)
      - Grocery Store. Golconda, Nevada (CP-50) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - Harvard, Illinois (880-138) Reproducible (plus) print, 1980 August (Box 91)
      - Homes beside Long Island Expressway. Bayside, Queens, New York (174-227) Reproducible print, 1974 January (Box 91)
      - Housing Development. Tempe, Arizona (678-1039) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Hudson River Reserve Fleet. Jones Point, New York (HRRF) Study print, 1961 (Box 91)
      - Hudson River Reserve Fleet. Jones Point, New York (HRRF) Study print, 1961 (Box 91)
      - Hudson River Reserve Fleet. Jones Point, New York (HRRF) Study print, 1961 (Box 91)
      - Hudson River Reserve Fleet. Jones Point, New York (HRRF) Study print, 1961 (Box 91)
      - Hudson River Reserve Fleet. Jones Point, New York (HRRF) Study print, 1961 (Box 91)
      - Husdon River Reserve Fleet. Jones Point, New York (No number extant) Study print, 1961 (Box 91)
      - I.O.O.F. Hall. Saco, Montana (CP-1018) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - I.O.O.F. Hall. Saco, Montana (CP-1018) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - I-20, I-75, I-85 Interchange. Atlanta, Georgia (HDP-4021) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 91)
      - I-70. Colorado (678-798) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - I-75. Northeast of Atlanta, Georgia (HDP-4298) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 91)
      - I-75/I-85. Atlanta, Georgia (HDP-4294-4) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 91)
      - I-84. Hartford, Connecticut (HDP-49) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 (Box 91)
      - Irrigated Fields. Arizona (678-133) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - John M. Caffrey, Conductor, Lehigh Valley Train #26, the "Asa Parker." Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania (LV) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 91)
      - Keokuk, Iowa (CP-1224) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - LaCrosse, Wisconsin (CP-254A) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - Lake Michigan, Looking South From Naubinway, Michigan (680-623) Reproducible print, 1980 June (Box 91)
      - Lake Michigan. From Whiting, Indiana (1180-115) Reproducible print, 1980 November (Box 91)
      - Lake Superior at Porcupine Mountains State Park. Michigan (680-701) Reproducible print, 1980 June (Box 91)
      - Lanark, Illinois (969-1250) Reproducible print, 1969 September (Box 91)
      - Looking Toward Copper Smelter. Miami, Arizona (678-266) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Lordville, New York (969-636) Reproducible print, 1969 September (Box 91)
      - Malta, Colorado (678-112) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Manhasset, New York (174-383) Reproducible print, 1974 January (Box 91)
      - Manhattan Skyline (Pre-World Trade Center) from Jersey Central Railroad Yards. Jersey City, New Jersey (NJ-164-73) Reproducible print, 1964 January (Box 91)
      - Mohawk, New York (1073-334) Reproducible print, 1973 October (Box 91)
      - Mohawk, New York (1073-328) Reproducible print, 1973 October (Box 91)
      - Mormac Swan Being Placed Into Moth Balls at Hudson River Reserve Fleet. Jones Point, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1961 (Box 91)
      - Near Brimfield, Peoria County, Illinois (CP-858) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - Near Peotone, Illinois (281-184) Reproducible print, 1981 February (Box 91)
      - Near Peotone, Will County, Illinois (281-86) Reproducible print, 1981 February (Box 91)
      - Near Picacho, Arizona (678-783) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - New Brunswick, New Jersey (273-49) Reproducible print, 1973 February (Box 91)
      - New Croton Reservoir Dam, New Croton Reservoir. Croton, New York (665-281) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 91)
      - New Croton Reservoir Dam, New Croton Reservoir. Croton, New York (665-280) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 91)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry. Spare Boat Orange, Tied-Up, Looking Southeast from Incoming Boat. Beacon, New York (NBF-361) Study print, 1961 March 25 (Box 91)
      - Northbrook, Illinois (281-111) Reproducible print, 1981 February (Box 91)
      - Ore Dock. Superior, Wisconsin (679-795) Reproducible (plus) print, 1979 June (Box 91)
      - Pollution, Kennebec River. Augusta, Maine (969-1644) Reproducible print, 1969 September (Box 91)
      - Pullman, Washington (CP-454) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - Rear of Diner, Route 22. Hillsdale, New Jersey (1265-140) Reproducible print, 1965 December (Box 91)
      - Republic Open Pit Taconite Mine (iron ore). Upper Peninsula, Michigan (680-815) Reproducible print, 1980 June (Box 91)
      - RMS Queen Mary, Arriving in New York on Next to Last Westbound Crossing. New York, New York (NYH-867-87) Reproducible print, 1967 August (Box 91)
      - Roadside Signs by I-70. Colorado (678-131) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Sandusky, Ohio (969-915) Reproducible print, 1969 September (Box 91)
      - Secaucus, New Jersey (174-53) Reproducible (plus) print, 1974 January (Box 91)
      - Secaucus, New Jersey (174-48) Reproducible print, 1974 January (Box 91)
      - Shopping Center. Tucson, Arizona (678-1057) Reproducible (plus) print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Shopping Center. Beaver Dam, Wisconsin (481-461) Reproducible print, 1981 April (Box 91)
      - State House. Atlanta, Georgia (HDP-3699) Study print, 1966 (Box 91)
      - Steamer William A. Irvin, Great Lakes Fleet. Superior, Wisconsin (679-851) Reproducible print, 1979 June (Box 91)
      - Steamers (Liners) Rafaello and Oceanic. Hudson River, New York, New York (JCM-1503) Reproducible (plus) print, 1974 (Box 91)
      - Steel Mills. Weirton, West Virginia (GFB-68-1098) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 91)
      - Steel Mills, Indiana Harbor Canal. East Chicago, Indiana (IS-378) Reproducible print, 1979 (Box 91)
      - Street by Abandoned Textile Mills. New Bedford, Massachusetts (475-616) Reproducible print, 1975 April (Box 91)
      - Superior, Arizona (678-1102) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Tamaqua, Pennsylvania (CP-1469) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - Tank Farm. Near Dubuque, Iowa (881-897) Reproducible print, 1981 August (Box 91)
      - Ted Tingle, Pilot, Tugboat J.W. Barta. Mississippi River (874-1528) Reproducible print, 1974 August (Box 91)
      - The Fort Pitt Bridge. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (PB-567-1597) Reproducible print, 1967 May (Box 91)
      - Towing "Dead" Liberty Ship From Hudson River Reserve Fleet to New York To Be Loaded With Surplus Government Grain. Jones Point, New York (HRRF) Study print, 1961 (Box 91)
      - Town Hall, H.H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1965 (Box 91)
      - Track Laying Gang, Penn-Central Railroad. Near Cresson, Pennsylvania (875-275) Reproducible print, 1975 August (Box 91)
      - Trailer. Miami, Arizona (678-912) Reproducible (plus) print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - Trash in a pond behind U.S. Steel, Gary Works. Gary, Indiana (GL-473-181) Reproducible print, 1973 April (Box 91)
      - U.S. Gypsum Company Building. Chicago, Illinois (581-50) Reproducible print, 1981 May (Box 91)
      - Valmy, Nevada (CP-1393) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 91)
      - View From Holiday Inn. Tucson, Arizona (678-168) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 91)
      - West Street. New York, New York (HDP-941) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 91)
      - Whitman County, Washington (972-375) Reproducible print, 1972 September (Box 91)
      - Young Maples, Plowden Farm. Vermont (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 91)
      - Abandoned Ferry. Ellis Island, New York (NYHFB-EI-562) Reproducible (plus) print, 1962 May (Box 92)
      - Ann Arbor Railroad, Ann Arbor Number 5, Lake Michigan car ferry. Manitowoc, Wisconsin (964-477) Reproducible print, 1964 September (Box 92)
      - Baltimore Ohio Railroad. Piedmont, West Virginia (464-229) Reproducible print, 1964 April (Box 92)
      - Boston Maine Railroad Station (abandoned). Greenfield, Massachusetts (MH-1163-7) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 92)
      - Boxcar Graffitti, Missouri Pacific Railroad Yards. Washington, Missouri (874-164) Reproducible print, 1974 August (Box 92)
      - Boxcar, Naperville Junction Railway. Oneonta, New York (D, 1975 (Box 92)
      - Burlington Northern Railroad Ore Train. Allouez, Wisconsin (679-983) Reproducible print, 1979 June (Box 92)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway #1262, Last Week of Steam Operation. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-1262) Reproducible print, 1960 March (Box 92)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway 4-6-2 Type Locomotives, The "Glen", Last Week of Steam Operation. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-3-1-60) Study print, 1960 March (Box 92)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway Locomotive No. 5145, St. Luc Terminal, Last Week of Steam Operation. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-5145) Reproducible print, 1960 March (Box 92)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, G-3 Class 4-6-2. #2408. Vaudreuil, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-Vaudreuil) Reproducible print, 1960 March (Box 92)
      - Car ferry SS Chief Wawatam. Saint Ignace, Michigan (975-996) Reproducible print, 1975 September (Box 92)
      - Chesapeake Ohio Railroad Yard. Thurmond, West Virginia (374-1279) Reproducible print, 1974 March (Box 92)
      - Chessie System (Chesapeake Ohio/Baltimore Ohio Railroad), Hopper Car (D, 1975 (Box 92)
      - Coal Breaker. West Virginia (1589) Reproducible print, undated (Box 92)
      - Coal Train. Near Pocahontas, Virginia (374-805) Reproducible print, 1974 March (Box 92)
      - Commuters, Lackawanna Railroad, Hoboken Ferry (NYH-FB/DL-168) Reproducible print, 1960 (Box 92)
      - Delaware Hudson Railroad. Oneonta, New York (D, 1975 (Box 92)
      - Delaware Hudson Railroad Sanding-Diesel Unit. Mechanicville, New York (D, 1975 (Box 92)
      - Detroit River Car Ferry Huron, Built 1875, on Detroit River, Canadian National Railways (CF-DR-963-89) Reproducible print, 1963 September (Box 92)
      - Diesel-Electric Locomotive, Penn Central Railroad. Cresson, Pennsylvania (875-269) Reproducible print, 1975 August (Box 92)
      - Driving Wheels of Canadian Pacific #5145, Last Week of Operation. Saint Luc, Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-Drivers-5145) Study print, 1960 March (Box 92)
      - Edwin S. Bisso Ferry on Mississippi River. New Orleans, Louisiana (1064-627) Reproducible print, 1964 October (Box 92)
      - Erie Railroad (Erie Lackawanna) Freight Station (abandoned). Susquehanna, Pennsylvania (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 92)
      - Ferryboat Scranton, Wheelhouse, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-35) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 92)
      - Former Lake Superior Ishpeming Railroad, 2-80 Steam Locomotive used in excursion train service. Marquette, Michigan (679-953) Reproducible print, 1979 June (Box 92)
      - Former New York Central Railroad Depot. Newark, New York (WC-505) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 (Box 92)
      - Former Pennsylvania Railroad Depot. Falls Creek, Pennsylvania (1066-163) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 October (Box 92)
      - Fred J. Lewis, Freight Conductor, Delaware Hudson Railroad (D, 1975 (Box 92)
      - Fred J. Lewis, Freight Conductor, Delaware Hudson Railroad Hand Signal (D, 1975 (Box 92)
      - Fred J. Lewis, Freight Conductor, Delaware Hudson Railroad, Coupling (D, 1975 (Box 92)
      - Freight Train Arriving at Delaware Hudson Railroad Yard. Oneonta, New York (D, 1975 (Box 92)
      - Fueling Diesel Engine, Soo Line Railroad. Gladstone, Michigan (975-1293) Reproducible print, 1975 September (Box 92)
      - Great Northern Railway, Willman Division, Mainline. Near Doran, Minnesota (GFB-68-4256) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 92)
      - Illinois Central Gulf Railroad, Unit Coal Train. Ashkum, Illinois (1080-1) Reproducible print, 1980 October (Box 92)
      - Iron Horse Ramble, Reading Company. Port Clinton, Pennsylvania (RDG-21-1060) Reproducible print, 1960 October (Box 92)
      - J. Burton Ayers at Allouez Ore Docks, Superior Line (679-550) Reproducible print, 1979 June (Box 92)
      - Jersey City Terminal, Central Railroad of New Jersey. Jersey City, New Jersey (CNJ-467-93) Reproducible (plus) print, 1967 April (Box 92)
      - Julia C. Moran off Staten Island. Staten Island, New York (JCM-728) Reproducible print, 1974 (Box 92)
      - Julia C. Moran Tugboat. New York City Harbor, New York (JCM-1154) Reproducible print, 1974 (Box 92)
      - Julia C. Moran Tugboat. New York City Harbor, New York (JCM-806) Reproducible print, 1974 (Box 92)
      - Kansas Pacific Railroad (Union Pacific). Near Cheyenne Wells, Colorado (471-401) Reproducible print, 1971 April (Box 92)
      - Lehigh Valley Railroad Passenger Depot (since razed). Jim Thorpe, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-275) Reproducible print, 1963 October (Box 92)
      - Lone Star (964-891) Reproducible print, 1964 September (Box 92)
      - Missouri Pacific. Scott City, Kansas (GP-2212) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 92)
      - Missouri Pacific. Scott City, Kansas (GP-2213) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 92)
      - Missouri Pacific. Scott City, Kansas (GP-2212) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 92)
      - Mormacape Freighter, Gowanus Canal Basin. Brooklyn, New York (JCM-1113) Reproducible print, 1974 (Box 92)
      - MV Maksim Gorky. New York City Harbor, New York (JCM-952) Reproducible print, 1974 (Box 92)
      - Norfolk Western Railroad Yard. Bluefield, West Virginia (374-1621) Reproducible print, 1974 March (Box 92)
      - Norfolk Western Railway Coal Train. Near Tazewell, Virginia (???-805) Reproducible print, undated (Box 92)
      - "Bitts", Julia C. Moran(JCM-505) Reproducible print, 1974 (Box 92)